{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the capital of Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Tel Aviv",
        "2": "Haifa",
        "3": "Jerusalem",
        "4": "Beer Sheva"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Jerusalem"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year was the State of Israel established?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "1947",
        "2": "1948",
        "3": "1949",
        "4": "1950"
      },
      "correct_answer": "1948"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first Prime Minister of Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "David Ben-Gurion",
        "2": "Golda Meir",
        "3": "Moshe Sharett",
        "4": "Yitzhak Rabin"
      },
      "correct_answer": "David Ben-Gurion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the largest sea bordering Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Red Sea",
        "2": "Mediterranean Sea",
        "3": "Dead Sea",
        "4": "Sea of Galilee"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main official language of Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "English",
        "2": "Arabic",
        "3": "Hebrew",
        "4": "Russian"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Hebrew"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the national emblem of Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Star of David",
        "2": "Menorah",
        "3": "Israeli flag",
        "4": "Western Wall"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Menorah"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the highest mountain in Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Mount Tabor",
        "2": "Mount Carmel",
        "3": "Mount Meron",
        "4": "Mount Hermon"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Mount Hermon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who wrote the lyrics of Israel's national anthem?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Chaim Nachman Bialik",
        "2": "Naftali Herz Imber",
        "3": "David Ben-Gurion",
        "4": "Theodor Herzl"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Naftali Herz Imber"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the official currency of Israel?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Dollar",
        "2": "Euro",
        "3": "New Shekel",
        "4": "Lira"
      },
      "correct_answer": "New Shekel"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year was the peace treaty between Israel and Egypt signed?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "1967",
        "2": "1973",
        "3": "1979",
        "4": "1982"
      },
      "correct_answer": "1979"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Israel's main international airport?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Ben Gurion Airport",
        "2": "Sde Dov Airport",
        "3": "Ramon Airport",
        "4": "Haifa Airport"
      },
      "correct_answer": "Ben Gurion Airport"
    }
  ]
}